<IncludeGroup
	xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
	xmlns:xml="http://www.w3.org/XML/1998/namespace"
 	xmlns="http://sifassociation.org/SpecGen">

	<CodeSet>
		<Intro>
			<p>Code set denoting the effect a ScheduleEvent will have on
			the school's academic schedule. At present, only full-day events
			(i.e. the "EventDate" field is populated but "EventTime" isn't)
			can have any effect other than "noEffect".</p>
		</Intro>
		<ID>Schedule Effect</ID>
		<Values>
			<Value>
				<Code>NOEFFECT</Code>
				<Text>No Effect</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>This event has no effect on the school calendar.</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>   <!-- No Effect -->

			<Value>
				<Code>RENUMBER</Code>
				<Text>Renumber Days</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>This event causes the day rotation on the school calendar to
					be renumbered, starting with any academic days specified in
					ScheduleDayList.</p>
					<p>If any terms are included in ScheduleTermList, those
					terms are activated effective on the start date of this
					event.</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>  <!-- Renumber -->

			<Value>
				<Code>INSERT</Code>
				<Text>Insert Day</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>This event causes an insertion into the normal academic day
					rotation of the school calendar.</p>
					<p>Any academic days and bell schedules specified in ScheduleDayList
					and BellScheduleList are scheduled for the duration of this event, or school is
					cancelled if ScheduleDayList is omitted.</p>
					<p>After the event ends the academic day rotation resumes from the
					point at which it was interrupted. E.g. if it was Day 1
					before the event, then it will be Day 2 afterwards.</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>   <!-- Insert -->

			<Value>
				<Code>DISPLACE</Code>
				<Text>Displace Day</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>This event causes a displacement in the normal academic day
					rotation of the school calendar.</p>
					<p>Any academic days or bell schedules
				 	specified in ScheduleDayList and BellScheduleList are
					scheduled for the duration of this event, or school is
					cancelled if ScheduleDayList is omitted.</p>
					<p>After the event ends the rotation resumes from the point it would
					be at had the event not occurred. E.g. if it was Day 1
					before the event, and the event duration was 1 day, then it
					will be Day 3 afterwards; Day 2 is overwritten by the event.</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>

			<Value>
				<Code>ENDSCHEDULE</Code>
				<Text>End Schedule</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>This event terminates the academic schedule for any term(s)
					specified in ScheduleTermList, which is required when
					using this schedule effect.</p>
					<p>Used to terminate the academic day rotation prior to the end of term; e.g. 
					when the last week of term is used for impromptu non-academic activities.</p>
					<p>Note that events take effect at
					midnight on the start date, so the designated term(s) do not
					occur on the actual day of the endSchedule event (i.e. the
					day prior to the event's start date is the last day the
					term(s) are in session).</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>
	
			<Value>
				<Code>PAUSESCHEDULE</Code>
				<Text>Pause Schedule</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>Temporarily suspend the academic day rotation
					until a subsequent "resumeSchedule" event occurs.</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>

			<Value>
				<Code>RESUMESCHEDULE</Code>
				<Text>Resume Schedule</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>Resume an academic day rotation previously suspended using "pauseSchedule".</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>

			<Value>
				<Code>CANCEL</Code>
				<Text>Cancel Day</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>Cancel one or more academic days, specified in ScheduleDayList,
					that would normally occur on this date.</p>
					<p>This is generally used to partially cancel the
					school schedule on a given calendar date. To fully cancel
					school on date, use either the "insert" or "displace"
					schedule effect.</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>

			<Value>
				<Code>STARTTERM</Code>
				<Text>Start Term</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>Start one or more terms, specified in ScheduleTermList, on this date
					without changing the academic day rotation.</p>
					<p>A ScheduleTermList
					value is required when using this schedule effect.
					</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>

			<Value>
				<Code>ADD</Code>
				<Text>Additional Day</Text>
				<Description>
					<p>Set one or more additional academic days, specified in ScheduleDayList
					to apply to this calendar date in addition to those normally applied to
					the academic day rotation.</p>
					<p>This can also be used to schedule school on a day on which it would not normally occur, such
					as a weekend.</p>
					<p>As a convenience, RemoveScheduleDayList specifies a set of 
					academic days to be removed from the calendar while this event is in effect.</p>
				</Description>
			</Value>

			<Value>
				<Code>CUSTOM</Code>
				<Text>Custom Day Schedule</Text>
				<Description>
					This event replaces the normal day rotation for the event date
					with a custom set of SchedulePeriods and bell times.
				</Description>
			</Value>		
		</Values>
	</CodeSet>    <!-- Schedule Effect -->

</IncludeGroup>
